3, 2, 1
I'm planning the 100k party
and I'm thinking it's probably going to be New Year's Eve at my house
What are you waiting for?
Oh wow
Oh I love that, you can't
I love that
Any non-alcoholic ones?
I'm being side side
Thank you
Touch your timeline
Go on
Alright, hold me in
We'll see you tomorrow
Guys, for the video we're going to say hi
in 3, 2, 1
Say hi guys
Bye
Awesome, you look great guys, thank you
Have a good night guys
Thank you
Let's go
This one has a Bitcoin of 10k
A candle
Oh that's so pretty
And here is a big Bitcoin Bitcoin
There's a big Bitcoin Bitcoin
And here is a big Bitcoin
And here is everyone's filming
The camera
Oh wow
Oh that's the pool huh?
Yeah, this is coming out
Yes it is
That's so good
Thank you
You're gonna be
But it's gonna be cool though
Beautiful
Oh nice
How big
Let's go
What's the name called
people will come to the shooting booth
It's so pretty
It doesn't have a breath on the field.
Okay.
Hi, good evening.
Hi, I'm great.
How are you?
I'm great.
What can I get for you?
Would you like to try some special ones?
I will try a special one and one for my mom, non-alcoholic.
Non-alcoholic, okay.
And mine, whatever.
Would you like to have something with the blue curacao?
Would you like to have something with tequila, gin or vodka?
Vodka, please.
Alright, gotcha.
Thank you.
Tequila is for way later.
Okay, yeah, keep it, keep it.
Keep it simple.
That's true.
The night is young and still a little plenty of time.
It's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine
Oh yes, yes.
Thank you.
You too.
Oh wow, that's so cute.
That is so cute.
Oh my god, this is where he does all the pancast and stuff.
Yes, because I see that all the time.
I'm going to get a wine, I'll be right back.
So that's where we were, where the wine is.
Go to the back room, you're going to die.
Go.
Wow.
I'm going to get a wine.
This one is perfect.
It's just coming here and right here.
Oh.
Wow.
World's second or third one will need to connect to theOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOM
It's beautiful.
But more beautiful.
Oh, look at the ceiling.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
These floors have been brought from Spain.
No way.
Yeah.
This home has been...
What he did was all the staircase, all the margins originally considered.
That's the beauty of it.
You can do the other things.
This is the real McCoy.
This is the real McCoy of the years of Europe.
Look at the ceiling.
Wow.
This is like you were in a museum in Europe, right?
Yeah.
Versace did a mansion.
We used to have parties in Versace's mansion.
I went to the first parties.
But this party's better than anyone.
Because this is from the house before.
Magnificent.
He didn't do this.
This was here.
I was in the house.
18 years ago.
Okay.
I think that's a January one.
Good.
Good morning.
Thank you.
Okay, so, um, I had a January request.
We had a number of times.
Thank you!
The last thing is like, I do think we had a number of times.
It's crazy, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine,
OMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOM
This is magnificent. My mother, my family were very important. It's hundreds of years ago, but my grandmother had a laugh. Now that is magnificent. You can't replace that.
Look at this. This is amazing. But for the beauty of it, it's not the money, it's the beauty of it that he restored this home. Look how magnificent it is. These are the original shoppers.
It's so beautiful. It's so beautiful. It's so beautiful. It's so beautiful. It's so beautiful.
This is my home and the rest. I'll take one, thank you.
Maybe I'll take another dessert. You like this? This is some cheese with coconut and a little bread.
Okay. Thank you. Have a good night. You too.
You too.
It's so amazing. I told you that we've been through this river today. And then I said that the house is very rich.
And then I saw a huge house and thought that the boat is too big. It's not a boat. It's a boat.
And then... Here we are. Here we are. This is her. Usher. This is sailor's boat. It's so amazing.
It's so amazing. It's so big. It's so big.
It's so big.
Thank you.
Thank you for the people.
Thank you for the people who need to go to the river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river river
What's up, Gigi?
My man.
Good?
Man.
When it was 2020, the bitcoin price.
Yes.
He's looking at theOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOM
eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight
OMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOMOM
I'm so excited to be here!
You're a lot taller when you're not in the compartment!
Hi mom!
Hi!
I'm so excited to be here!
Wow!
You want to use this?
Yeah!
Thank you for having me!
Here's my second book!
Can you get a picture?
This is a girl!
I'm not a camera!
No, I'm a camera!
You're a sneaky girl!
She's so smart!
I'm so smart!
This year!
Yes!
Have you had a picture?
Yeah!
I'm so smart!
There you go!
Yes!
Thank you!
Thank you for having me.
Yeah.
Mission complete.